https://www.manderley.com/privacy-policy/

PRIVACY POLICY | Manderley
Natural Grass Sod, Seed, Fertilizer, Soil and Garden Products
Français
Search for:
1-888-225-3885
Order Sod Online!
MENU
Search for:
1-888-225-3885
Order Sod Online!
HOMEOWNERS
PROFESSIONALS
PRIVACY POLICY
Manderley > PRIVACY POLICY
You are welcome to visit Manderley.com while remaining anonymous and not revealing any personally identifying information. Providing us with your personal information is strictly voluntary. The following explains our policy with respect to any personal information you may provide to us when you visit our web site. If you do not agree with the terms of our privacy policy please do not use this web site.
How Personal Information is Collected and Used
Cookies are small text files that our web site asks to place on your computer’s hard drive. If your browser is set to accept cookies, then your browser adds the text in a small file. We use cookie technology when you request something from our web site, such as information about our products. We do not use cookies to read any other information on your computer’s hard drive. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies, or to warn you before a cookie is placed on your hard drive. If you choose not to accept cookies, you may have to manually input your user id and password or manually input information such as your name, email address and other optional information each time you want to receive information from our web site.
We collect personal information in order to provide you with information regarding our products. If you chose to provide personal information to Manderley, we will only use the information to provide you with the material that you have requested and to provide you with updates to that material or other material that we believe may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use this information as a basis for further contact with you, please advise and we will respect your wishes.
Manderley will not sell this personal information to other companies.
We also collect information which cannot be associated with you personally. This information is used to assess trends, statistics and customers’ needs, to help us improve our products and our web site.
Links to Other Web Sites
Our website contains links to other web sites. We cannot be responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other web sites.
Accuracy, Access and Opting Out
We will use all reasonable efforts to protect the quality and integrity of your personal information. If you wish to find out the details of any personal information we hold about you or if you wish to correct or update the personal information or have us delete that personal information, please contact us at info@manderley.com. If you have any concerns with our privacy policy or if you have any concerns with our use of your personal information, please contact us at info@manderley.com.
By using this site, you signify your agreement with the Manderley Privacy Policy. Manderley reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Use of Manderley.com is subject to the Terms of Use.
About Us
Products
Careers
Product Guides
Blog
Reviews
Contact Us
My Account
Privacy Policy
Français
Accessibility
Due to COVID-19 we are currently experiencing shipping delays – we’ll do everything we can to get your delivery to you as soon as possible. Thank you for your patience.
En raison de COVID-19, nous avons actuellement des retards de livraison – nous ferons tout notre possible pour que votre livraison vous soit livrée dès que possible. Merci pour votre patience.
×
×
